memuplay.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

### PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND OUR VIEWS AND PRACTICES REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND HOW WE WILL TREAT IT. TAKE A MOMENT TO FAMILIARIZE YOURSELF WITH OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES AND LET US KNOW IF YOU HAVE ANY CONCERNS.

This Privacy Policy describes Microvirt policies for collecting, using and disclosing your personal data. By using any of our product, you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. Microvirt is committed to respecting your privacy and maintaining accuracy, confidentiality and security of your personal information. We does not sell, share or distribute customer information to any third party organization. Microvirt collect contact information of those who communicate with us via e-mail or SNS and feedback information volunteered by the consumer via survey or post. The information we collect is used to improve the user experience of our product, and is not shared with or sold to any third organization for commercial purposes.

### WHAT WE DO

Microvirt only collect basic, non-personal technical information. By default, we collects statistics about your usage of our product, like software version, downloaded apps, apps usage time, which are anonymized before being sent.

### WHAT WE DON'T DO

Microvirt never sell your personal information. We don't automatically collect personal information without your permission, although we do automatically collect technical information about how users interact with our product, We don't track your activity across the internet, although we do receive and keep information about how you got our product.

* * *

### MICROVIRT FOLLOWS EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (“GDPR”)

Microvirt is committed to ensuring the security and protection of the personal information that we process, and to provide a compliant and consistent approach to the EU General Data Protection Regulation data protection. We recognise our obligations in updating and adjusting our data service to meet the demands of the GDPR.

### GENERAL INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT

We may collect your information when you view ads including the following: Device model, carrier, name and properties of mobile application through which a consumer interacts with the Advertising Services, country, time zone and locale settings (country and preferred language), network connection type, IP address, Internet browser user-agent used to access the Advertising Services, application version, the geo-location of your device (using GPS or other geo-location data) and the Google Advertising ID, device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.

### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The security of User’s information is our utmost priority, and we take strict measures in order to protect our data from unauthorized access, use, disclosure or destruction of data. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures for the Services that comply with applicable laws and industry standards. For example, we use firewalls, encryption technology and other automated software designed to protect against fraud and identity theft; our data is only stored in data center that provide high-level security for User’s information. Physical access is strictly controlled both ait the perimeter and at building ingress points by our staff utilizing video surveillance and other electronic means. We also protect User’s privacy by seeking to minimize the amount of sensitive data and PRI that we store on our servers in the first place.

* * *

### FOR ADDITIONAL QUESTION, PLEASE CONTACT SUPPORT@MICROVIRT.COM
